Oh, my God, we did it!
我的天啊，我們真的那麼做了
We just got married. Right there!
我們剛剛結婚了，就在那裡
Is that your ring?
那是你的戒指嗎？
We're off to a good start.
我們有個不錯的開始
-And, you sure you're not pregnant? -Yeah. I'm sure.
-你確定你沒有懷孕？ -我很確定
But if you're ready to have kids we got a room upstairs.
如果你準備好要生孩子 樓上有房間
I mean, I'll blow off this party right now. I'll do it!
我是說我會搞砸這個派對 我會那麼做的
Okay, you guys, that ceremony was so beautiful.
好了，大伙們 婚禮非常溫馨
Was it?! Was it perfect?! Is it too soon to see the video?!
是嗎？它很完美嗎？ 錄影帶沖洗好了嗎？
Can we just please take a moment? Our two best friends just got married.
大家能不能安靜一分鐘？ 我們兩個好朋友剛剛結婚
We are so blessed to be able to share in this incredible joy.
我們可以跟他們分享喜悅 真的非常幸運
That is so true.
一點都沒錯
Mon, is it too late to switch from chicken to steak?
摩妮卡，現在把雞肉 換成牛排太晚了吧？
I'm so happy for you guys. And you are both so lucky!
我為你們感到高興 你們太幸運了
I mean, you both said the right names
你們叫對了彼此的名字
And nobody was drunk.
沒有人喝醉
Okay.
好吧
And nobody was gay.
沒有人是同性戀
And on your first try.
這是你們的第一次婚姻
The One After I Do
本集播出：婚禮之後
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Great. Great. Just give me a sec to change film.
太棒了 讓我換一下底片
I know I'm not supposed to know, but I do and I'm so excited for you.
我知道你不希望我知道 但我知道了，我為你感到高興
-What's going on? -Monica's pregnant.
-發生了什麼事？ -摩妮卡懷孕了
Oh, my God. Is that why you guys had to get married?
天啊 所以你們兩個要結婚？
-Guys, I'm not pregnant. -Oh, slow swimmers?
-聽著，我沒有懷孕 -精子游得太慢了？
What?! What do you mean? You're not pregnant?
什麼？你是什麼意思？ 你沒有懷孕？
-You didn't tell anybody I was, did you? -No.
-你沒有告訴任何人我懷孕了吧？ -沒有
I'll be right back.
我馬上回來
You. Take a lot of pictures.
你，多拍一些照片
Why don't we get a shot of Monica and the bloody soldier.
我們為什麼不拍張 摩妮卡跟英勇士兵的合照？
About that, Joey, you have to change before the party.
關於那一點，喬伊 你得在婚宴開始前換套衣服
-I can't. I don't have any other clothes here. -Find some, please.
-我辦不到，我沒帶衣服來換 -拜託你去找套衣服
Anything that doesn't say, "I died tragically in France."
別再穿著 「我在法國戰死」的衣服
-Fine! -And be careful who you hug, okay?
-好吧 -不要亂抱任何人，好嗎？
My father's upstairs in tears because you got blood on his dress.
我爸在樓上哭得半死 因為你害他的禮服沾到了血
Why don't we see the bride and the groom, and the bridesmaids.
我們為什麼不讓新人 跟伴娘們合照一些照片？
Hey, Mon, why'd you tell the guys that you weren't pregnant?
摩妮卡，你為什麼告訴大家 你沒有懷孕？
-Because I'm not. -We found your tests.
-因為我沒有懷孕 -我們發現了你的驗孕棒
If you're not pregnant..
如果你沒有懷孕…
it's because I am.
那是因為我懷孕了
What are you talking about?
你在胡說什麼？
Yes, I am with child.
對，我懷了孩子
I didn't want to say anything because it's your day.
我不想說 因為今天是你們的大喜之日
-I didn't wanna steal your thunder. -So you told people I was pregnant?
-我不想搶了你的風采 -於是你告訴大家我懷孕了？
Does this look like a conversation I want to remember?
這是那種 我會想記住的對話嗎？
-Who's the father? -Yeah.
-孩子的爸是誰？ -對
I can't say.
我不能說
-Why? -Why not?
-為什麼？ -為什麼不行？
I can't say because he's famous.
我不能說，因為他是名人
Oh, my God. Who is it?
天啊，他是誰？
Phoebe, come on, you have to tell us.
菲比，你得告訴我們
Okay, okay, it's James Brolin.
好吧，是詹姆斯布洛林
James Brolin is the father of my baby.
詹姆斯布洛林是孩子的爸爸
As in Barbra Streisand's husband James Brolin?
你是說芭芭拉史翠珊的老公 詹姆斯布洛林？
What?!
什麼？
Well, he never said that to me.
他一直都沒有告訴我
Monica, if you step away, we'll get Chandler and the bridesmaids.
摩妮卡，請你先離開 我們要拍錢德跟伴娘的合照
How about just the bridesmaids?
何不只拍伴娘的合照呢？
I am the groom. I was told it was a big deal.
我是伴郎 聽說這個位置很重要
-It is. -Yeah.
-沒錯 -對
Oh, my God.
天啊
Thank you for that. I can't deal with the stress quite yet.
謝謝你 我還沒有辦法承受那樣的壓力
Instead you told me Monica was pregnant?
於是你告訴我 摩妮卡懷孕了？
You said she was. I didn't disagree with you.
是你說她懷孕了 我沒有反駁你
Sneaky.
很狡猾吧
Smile, ladies!
笑一個，小姐們
-By the way, James Brolin? -I know.
-對了，詹姆斯布洛林？ -我知道
I could only think of two names: him and Ed Begley Jr.
我腦海裡浮起兩個人名 他跟小艾德貝格利
-Then I remembered he's gay, so.. -Ed Begley Jr. is not gay.
-然後我想起來他是男同志，所以… -小艾德貝格利不是男同志
Really?
真的嗎？
Congratulations!
恭喜
Look who's married! And just in time too, I hear.
看看誰結婚了 我聽說你們是奉子成婚
What? Ross!
什麼？羅斯
So if you've got this all under control, I'm just gonna..
如果你不去好好解釋 我會…
I just wanted you to know that you have made us happier
我只是要你知道 你讓我們更快樂了
You have given us more joy..
你讓我們更加高興…
I'm not pregnant.
我沒有懷孕
What?
什麼？
I'm not pregnant.
我沒有懷孕
Oh, well.
好吧
But I did still get married today.
但我今天還是結婚了
Whatever.
隨便
Thank you very much.
謝謝
Ladies and gentlemen, it gives me great pleasure to introduce to you:
各位先生女士 我很榮幸跟大家介紹
Mr. and Mrs. Chandler Bing.
錢德賓夫婦
-Before we go out there, I got a present. -I'm not gonna put my hand in your pocket.
-到舞池前我要送你一份禮物 -我不想把手伸到你的口袋裡
-No. I've been taking dancing lessons. -What?
-不，我去上了舞蹈課 -什麼？
For the last six weeks. I wanted this to be a moment you'd never forget.
我上了六星期的舞蹈課 我希望這一刻能讓你永生難忘
That is so sweet.
那真的是太體貼了
So would you care to join me in our first dance as husband and wife?
你願不願意以夫妻的身份 跟我跳第一隻舞？
Yes.
我願意
-What's the matter? -It's these new shoes, they're all slippery.
-怎麼了？ -我的新鞋太滑了
-Are you gonna be able to do this? -Not well.
-你能跳舞嗎？ -不太行
Well, the good news is, I don't think anyone's looking at us.
好消息是 我想沒有人在看我們
So are you ready to talk about it?
你準備要談了嗎？
No.
不
Now?
現在呢？
No!
不
-We'll talk about something else then. -Thank you.
-我們來談別的事 -謝謝
Who's the father?
孩子的爸是誰？
Honey, I haven't told him yet..
甜心，我還沒有告訴他…
so, until I do, I don't think I should tell anybody else.
我打算先告訴他 再告訴其他人
That's fine. That's fair.
沒關係，那很公平
-Is it Tag? -Phoebe!
-是泰格嗎？ -菲比
Okay, I'm sorry. I'll stop.
好吧，對不起，我不說了
Is it Ross? It's Ross, isn't it?
是羅斯嗎？是羅斯吧？
-Oh, my God, it's Joey! -Stop it. Okay?
-天啊，是喬伊 -別說了，好嗎？
I am not gonna tell you until I tell him.
在告訴他之前 我不會告訴你的
At least we know it's a him.
至少我們知道他是個男的
Oh, sweet Lord.
天啊
I'm sorry, okay? I went down to the gift shop.
對不起，好嗎？ 我跑到禮品店
It was either this or a bathrobe. What's more important:
那裡只賣這個跟浴袍 什麼事比較重要呢？
The way I'm dressed, or being with you today?
我的穿著打扮 還是我今天能夠出席？
Honey, I'm not gonna even pretend I was listening. Hey! Hey!
我不會假裝 我聽到你說什麼
I'm Ross, I don't believe we met. I'm Monica's older brother.
我是羅斯，我相信我們沒有見過 我是摩妮卡的哥哥
Hi, I'm Mona from her restaurant.
我是她在餐廳的同事蒙娜
Hello, Mona from her restaurant.
你好，她在餐廳的同事蒙娜
Mona. What a beautiful name.
蒙娜，這個名字很美
You think so? I always kind of hated it.
你真的那麼想？ 我一直都很討厭這個名字
Come on! Mona Lisa.
少來了，蒙娜麗莎
Mona...
蒙娜…
Llegglachen.
利格拉齊
The famous botanist.
她是著名的植物學家
Oh, no, she's.. Well, she's dead now, but..
不，她… 她死了，但是…
Supposedly she was once quite the hottie of the plant world.
她曾經是植物學界 最性感的女人
Really?
真的嗎？
-See, I never knew about her. -Linda Llegglachen..
-我根本不認識她 -琳達利格拉齊…
So, what table are you at?
你在幾號桌？
Me too.
我也是
Good. Now there'll be someone there who likes my name.
很好，那麼有個喜歡我名字的人 會跟我同桌
Yes, there will.
對，沒錯
Guess what, Molly Gilbert. You've just been bumped up to table one.
猜怎麼了？茉莉吉柏特 你剛剛被踢到一號桌
And if it's all right with you, I'll take your place at table six.
如果你沒有意見的話 我要代替你坐到六號桌
Martin Llegglachen.
馬丁利格拉齊
That's better. Now, just bend your arms a little bit. Now look straight ahead.
那樣子好多了，現在雙手彎曲 眼睛看前方
This time I want you to really put your ass into it.
這次我要你 臀部用力頂
Who's slippery now?
看你還滑不滑？
Isn't that just the best feeling? Rubbing a fork on the bottom of your shoe?
那真的很棒吧？ 拿叉子去磨你的鞋底？
Chandler, darling, look, my date has finally arrived.
錢德，你看 我的男伴終於來了
I'd like you to meet Dennis Phillips. Dennis, this is my son, Chandler.
我要你見見丹尼斯菲利浦斯 丹尼斯，他是我兒子錢德
-Congratulations. -Thank you.
-恭喜 -謝謝
Dennis is a dear old friend..
丹尼斯是我的老朋友…
and a fantastic lover.
跟好情人
Are my ears bleeding?
我的耳朵在流血嗎？
Don't mind Chandler. He's always been shy.
別理錢德 他一向都很害羞
Oh, you're right.
你說的對
Bravo, Dennis. Thanks for pleasing my mother so.
太棒了，丹尼斯 謝謝你取悅我老媽
I'm so sorry I missed the ceremony. I was stuck at auditions.
抱歉我沒趕上婚禮 我忙著在試鏡
Yes, Dennis is directing a new Broadway show.
對，丹尼斯正在執導 一出百老匯新戲
I don't believe we've met. Joey Tribbiani.
我不敢相信能見到你 喬伊崔比亞尼
-Dennis Phillips. -I've admired your work for years.
-丹尼斯菲利浦斯 -多年來我一直很仰慕你的成就
-You've done some really amazing stuff. -Thank you.
-你真的很棒 -謝謝
If you'll excuse me, I'm gonna go get myself a drink.
對不起 我要去喝點東西
I'll be back in a moment.
我馬上回來
Okay. You stop.
好吧，別鬧了
Dennis Phillips. That's great. How did you guys meet?
丹尼斯菲利浦斯，那真的是太棒了 你們怎麼認識的？
-Well, it's a funny story. -Funny, "ha-ha"? Or funny:
-那是個有趣的故事 -是普通有趣還是爆笑？
Thank you. If everyone will please take your seats, dinner will be served.
謝謝，大家請坐 晚宴馬上開始
-I thought you were at table six. -No. Nine.
-我以為你在六號桌 -不，是九號桌
See, before, when you showed it to me, you held it that way..
你剛剛拿給我看時 是那樣子拿的…
which was misleading.
我被你誤導了
Hello.
哈囉
Will you see if your mom can give my resume to Dennis Phillips?
你能請你媽把我的履歷表 拿給丹尼斯菲利浦斯嗎？
Well, they've kind of locked themselves in one of the men's room stalls right now.
他們正把自己 鎖在男洗手間裡
Perhaps when they get out.
或許等他們出來再說
If I could get in a Broadway show, then I would've done it all.
只要能演百老匯舞台劇 我什麼戲都能演
Film, television and theater.
電影，電視劇跟舞台劇
The only thing left would be radio. But that's just for ugly people.
唯一例外是廣播劇 因為那是給醜八怪演的
-What size shoes do you wear? -Eleven,11.
-你穿幾號鞋？ -11，11號半
My shoes give me a problem on the dance floor. Can I borrow your boots?
我的鞋子太滑沒辦法跳舞 你的戲靴能借我嗎？
I don't really even know where I left those.
我真的不知道 我把靴子丟到哪裡去了
-Those aren't 11 . -Okay, fine, I'm a 7!
-你的腳不可能是11號半 -好吧，我穿七號的鞋子
I have surprisingly small feet. But the rest of me is good. I'll show you.
我的腳非常小 但其他部份都很大，我可以露給你看
Who am I kidding? I belong in radio.
我在跟誰開玩笑呢？ 我應該去演廣播劇
-Can you believe Phoebe got pregnant? -Let's not talk about that right now.
-你能相信菲比懷孕了嗎？ -現在別談那件事
-This is so huge. -Sure, but as big as your wedding?
-這是大消息 -沒錯，但它沒有你的婚禮重要
Of course not. Nothing is.
當然，我的婚禮是最重要的
Between me and you, in this day and age..
這是我們私下的談話 到了這個時代…
how dumb do you have to be to get pregnant?
誰會笨到 讓自己懷孕？
Sometimes you can do everything right. Everyone wears what they're supposed to..
有時候你該做的都做了 大家都戴上他們該戴的東西…
and one of those little guys just gets through.
但有個小傢伙 還是攻過了城池
-How? -I don't know. Maybe they have tools.
-怎麼會呢？ -我不知道，或許它們有工具
Well, I talked to her, and she's definitely gonna have the baby.
我跟她談過 她想留下孩子
She said she's gonna raise it on her own.
她說 她要自己撫養孩子
-Well, maybe that's really brave. -Maybe.
-或許那真的很勇敢 -或許吧
I just hope she realizes how hard it's gonna be.
我只是希望 她知道那有多辛苦
Maybe she hasn't really thought it through that much.
或許她沒有 想那麼多
Well, there's a lot to think about.
的確有很多事需要考慮
How is she gonna handle this financially? How is she gonna juggle work?
她要怎麼處理經濟問題？ 她怎麼有辦法去工作？
Does she realize she's not gonna have a date again for the next, like,18 years?
她知道她在未來的18年內 都無法再去約會了嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道
Are you okay?
你沒事吧？
I'm just thinking about Phoebe. Poor, knocked-up Phoebe.
我只是想到了菲比 懷了孕的可憐菲比
-Champagne? -Oh, yes! Thank you very much.
-要喝香檳嗎？ -好的，謝謝你
That's actually how the French drink it.
法國人都是那樣喝香檳的
Well, I just got off the phone with my lover James Brolin.
我剛剛跟我的情人 詹姆斯布洛林通過電話
-Oh, really? -Apparently, he is married to some singer.
-真的嗎？ -很明顯地他娶了一個歌手
But he said he'd leave her for me. And I said, "James Brolin, are you sure?"
但他說他會為了我離開她 我說「詹姆斯布洛林，你確定嗎？」
-James Brolin said.. -Rachel's the one who's pregnant?
-詹姆斯布洛林說… -懷孕的人是瑞秋？
What?!
什麼？
Why bother?
幹嘛那麼麻煩呢？
-How do you feel? -I don't know how I feel.
-你覺得如何？ -我不知道我有什麼感覺
This is all happening so fast. I have to make all these decisions that I don't wanna make.
一切發生的太快 我得做出這些我不想做的決定
Someone just take this away from me!
快把這玩意拿走
-Calm down. Maybe you're not pregnant. -What?!
-冷靜點，或許你沒有懷孕 -什麼？
When I got pregnant with the triplets, I took that test, like, three times.
我懷三胞胎時 也驗了三次孕才確定
Yes. Maybe it's a false positive. Are you sure you peed on the stick right?
對，或許是假警報 你確定你尿在驗孕棒的方式沒錯？
How many ways are there to do that?
不然我要怎麼尿才對？
I'm just saying, don't freak out until you're 100 percent sure.
我是說沒有百分之百確定前 別大驚小怪
All right, I'll take it again when I get home.
好吧 我回家後會再驗一次
I can wait until then.
我可以等到那時候再說
Oh, this is such a good party. How late does it go till?
這個派對很棒 它什麼時候會結束？
-You gotta take it now. -No, this your wedding.
-你可以現在驗 -不，這是你的婚禮
You're not gonna be able to have fun until we know. Do it as a present to me.
沒有確定前你根本無法盡興地玩 就把它當成送我的禮物吧
Okay, thank you.
好吧，謝謝你
-I'll run out and get you one. -You girls are so great.
-我去幫你買驗孕棒 -你們真的是太好了
-Wait a minute. Who's the father? -She won't tell us.
-等一下，孩子的爸是誰？ -她不肯告訴我們
Come on! It's my wedding. That could be my present!
快說吧，這是我的婚禮 你可以當做是送我的禮物
-I just gave you peeing on a stick. -See, this is why you register.
-我剛剛答應為了你驗孕 -看吧，所以一定要有禮物清單
It was the chair again. Okay? I'm not doing it!
又是椅子的聲音，好嗎？ 不是我幹的
Dad. Can't you go back to your table?
老爹，你不能回你的桌子去嗎？
No. Apparently little Molly Gilbert is enjoying her grown-up salmon en croute.
不，很明顯地小茉莉吉柏特 正開心地吃她的大號鮭魚開胃菜
Look, I don't.. You know what?
聽著，我沒有… 你知道嗎？
-Would you like to dance? -Sure.
-你想跳舞嗎？ -好啊
Great.
太棒了
-Dr. Geller. -I wasn't farting!
-蓋勒博士 -我沒有放屁
A little game from our table.
那是我們那一桌玩的小遊戲
Dr. Geller, will you dance with me?
蓋勒博士，你願意跟我跳舞嗎？
Maybe later. Right now, I'm about to dance with this lady.
或許待會再說 現在我要跟這位小姐跳舞
Unless this lady wouldn't mind letting you go first.
除非這位小姐不介意 讓你插隊
I'd be happy to. You are very sweet.
我很樂意 你太好心了
Yes, I am.
沒錯
In fact, let's try my special way. You can dance on my feet.
事實上我們來試試我的絕招 你可以踩在我的腳上跳舞
-Sure. -Yeah? Hop on.
-沒問題 -是嗎？跳上來吧
Is the pretty lady looking? Keep dancing.
那個美麗的小姐在看嗎？ 繼續跳
And the world will never know.
誰想得到呢？
Did you talk to Dennis about me yet?
你跟丹尼斯提過我的事了嗎？
I told him how talented you were and all about Days of our Lives.
我跟他提到你非常有天份 還有《我們的日子》的事
You don't tell a Broadway guy that! Now he thinks I'm just a soap actor.
你不能告訴百老匯導演那種事 現在他會以為我是肥皂劇演員
But you're not just a soap actor.
但你不只是肥皂劇演員
You are a soap actor with freakishly tiny feet.
你是有雙小腳的 肥皂劇演員
He has no idea what kind of range I have.
他不知道 我有多厲害
Don't move.
別動
It's like he's running on tiny little pegs.
那像是他用 小腳在跑步
-Thank you. -No, thank you, Miranda.
-謝謝 -不，謝謝你，米蘭達
-Melinda. -All right.
-是梅玲達 -好吧
-How cute was that? -Oh, were you watching?
-那真的好可愛 -你在看我們嗎？
Can I go next?
下一個是我嗎？
Of course you can. Hop on.
當然是，來吧
Okay, but I get to hop on after her.
好吧，但我要排在她後面
-I am so gonna score. -What?
-我一定能得分 -什麼？
I like your bow.
我喜歡你的蝴蝶結
I'd like to propose a toast to Monica and Chandler..
我要請大家舉杯 向摩妮卡及錢德致意…
the greatest couple in the world, and my best friends.
他們是全世界最速配的夫妻 也是我最好的朋友
When I first found out they were getting married, I was a little angry.
我剛聽說他們要結婚時 我非常生氣
I was like, "Why, God? Why? How can you take them away from me!"
我心想「天啊，為什麼？ 你為什麼要把他們從我身邊搶走？」
But then I thought back over all our memories together. Some happy memories.
然後我回想起我們之間所有的回憶 快樂的回憶
And there were some sad memories.
跟悲傷的回憶
I'm sorry.
對不起
And some scared memories.
可怕的回憶
And then I realized I'll always be their friend.
然後我瞭解到 我永遠都會是他們的朋友
Their friend who can speak in many dialects..
他們的朋友 能說許多台詞…
and has training in stage combat and is willing to do partial nudity.
接受過舞台打鬥訓練 願意拍部份裸露的戲
To the happy couple.
敬這對金童玉女
-Thank you. -That was very nice, Ashley.
-謝謝 -那真的是太棒了，艾許莉
-Can we do it again? -No, no.
-我們能再跳一次嗎？ -不
-So, is it my turn now? -I'm next.
-現在輪到我了嗎？ -我是下一個
-That's okay, you can dance with her first. -Are you sure?
-沒關係，你可以先跟她跳 -你確定？
-So, what's your name? -Gert.
-你叫什麼名字？ -葛特
That's pretty.
那個名字很美
What are you doing there, Gert?
你在做什麼？葛特
Dancing on your feet like the other girls did it.
跟其他女孩一樣 踩在你腳上跳舞
好吧
Hop on, Gert.
跳上來吧，葛特
-Why aren't you moving your feet? -I'm trying.
-你的腳為什麼不動？ -我在努力了
Faster. You're not going fast enough.
快一點，你跳的太慢了
Maybe I should stand on your feet!
或許我該踩在你腳上
So did you happen to catch my toast up there?
你有聽到 我的致詞了嗎？
-Oh, my God. That was for my benefit? -There was a little something for everyone.
-天啊，你那麼做是為了我？ -我那麼做是為了所有人
-I know you're casting for this new show. -I don't think you're right for this project.
-我知道你在為新戲選角 -我想你不適合這個計劃
You're wrong.
你錯了
Whatever it is, I can do it. If you didn't see it up there, just try me.
不論內容是什麼，我都辦得到 如果你對剛剛的表演不滿意，考考我
It's an all Chinese cast. Can you be Chinese?
那齣戲的演員全是中國人 你可以變成中國人嗎？
-Well, I'm not proud of this, but.. -Oh, my God. Please don't!
-我不以此為榮，但是… -天啊，求求你別那麼做
-Ready to get back to the dance floor? -Did it turn into sand?
-準備重回舞池了嗎？ -它變成沙地了嗎？
-Come on, I love this song. You'll be fine. -No. No, I won't.
-我喜歡這首歌，你會跳得很好的 -不，我不會的
Do you know why I took all those lessons?
你知道為什麼 我要去上舞蹈課嗎？
I didn't want you to be embarrassed to be seen on the dance floor..
我不希望你被看到 跟一個笨拙的白癡跳舞…
with some clumsy idiot.
丟光了臉
Oh, sweetie, you could never embarrass me.
甜心 你不可能讓我出糗
Okay, you could easily embarrass me. But it doesn't matter, all right?
好吧，你很容易就會讓我出糗 但那不重要，好嗎？
I married you.
我嫁給你
No matter what you do, I'm gonna come home with you, okay?
不論你做什麼 我會跟你回家，好嗎？
So I'm gonna dance on my wedding night with my husband. Come on.
我要在新婚之夜 跟我丈夫跳舞，來吧
But I'll tell you, that's the last time I buy shoes at the Slippery Fun Shoe store.
但我告訴你，那是我最後一次 在"超滑鞋店"買鞋子
Just try not to move your feet at all.
盡量不要移動你的腳
There you go.
就是那樣
-I'm gonna have you arrested. -Why?
-我要逮捕你 -為什麼？
You stole my moves!
你偷走了我的舞步
Oh, Chandler, you're quite the dancer!
錢德，你是跳舞高手
-Thanks, Mrs. Geller. -Oh, come on, you can call me Mom.
-謝謝你，蓋勒太太 -少來了，你可以叫我媽媽
Really?
真的嗎？
I will.
我會的
Sorry, Mom.
抱歉，媽媽
-How much longer? -30 seconds.
-還要多久？ -30秒
Thirty seconds, okay..
30秒，好吧…
Did I miss it?
我錯過了嗎？
I want you to know that if it's positive, we're gonna..
我要你知道如果是陽性反應 我們得…
-I know. I know. -You do. Okay.
-我知道 -你知道，好吧
It's time.
時候到了
不准進來
Go ahead, Rach.
來吧，瑞秋
Wait. You know what? I can't look at it. Somebody else tell me.
等一下，知道嗎？我不敢看 誰幫我看一下
It's negative.
是陰性反應
-What? -It's negative.
-什麼？ -是陰性反應
Well, there you go.
真相揭曉
That is.. That's great. That is really great, great news.
那…那真的是太棒了 這真是個天大的好消息
You know, because the whole..
因為這整件事…
not being ready and, kind of, the financial aspects, all that..
在經濟方面我還沒有準備好 所以…
This is so just the way that this was supposed to be.
事情本來就應該 是這樣的
Then, great.
那麼說的話，太棒了
God, this is so stupid.
天啊，這真的是太愚蠢了
How can I be upset over something I never had?
我怎麼會為了 我從來沒有擁有過的東西難過？
-It's negative? -No, it's positive.
-是陰性反應嗎？ -不，是陽性反應
-What? -It's not negative, it's positive.
-什麼？ -不是陰性反應，是陽性反應
-Are you sure? -Yeah, I lied before.
-你確定？ -對，剛剛我說謊
-Now you know how you really feel about it. -That's a risky little game.
-現在你知道你真正的感覺了 -那是個危險的小把戲
Are you really gonna do this?
你真的要這麼做？
Yeah.
對
I'm gonna have a baby.
我要生下孩子
I'm gonna have a baby!
-With who? -No, it's still not the time.
-孩子的爸是誰？ -不，現在還不是時候
I just didn't see the fast song coming.
我不知道接下來是快歌
Don't talk, we'll get you up to your room, soak your feet. You'll be okay.
別說話，我們送你回房間 讓你泡泡腳，你會沒事的
-Thank you. -That is so sweet!
-謝謝 -那真的是太好心了
No, I mean it. There are so few genuinely nice guys out there.
不，我是認真了 現在好男人不多了
Tell me about it. I feel like I'm holding down the fort by myself.
你說的對 我覺得自己像是死守碉堡的士兵
-It's Joey, right? -Yeah.
-你是喬伊，對吧？ -對
Wait a minute! No!
等一下，不
I'm the nice one!
我才是好人
I'm the one that danced with the kids all night. I..
是我整晚跟孩子們跳舞 我…
How small are your feet?!
你的腳好小